

ABOUT

With over 8 years in both fields I've become dedicated to both sides of UI design and coding well optimized and interactive websites.

And devoting my time into learning new technolgies on improving user experiences on the web, and providing visually pleasing user interfaces and designs that make an impact to not be forgetten.

CONTACT



dbaker@live.ca



519.582-3912



www.darylbaker.ca

SOCIAL

facebook.com/daryl.w.baker

twitter.com/dimerbox

github.com/dimerbox



SKILLSETS

EXPERT KNOWLEDGE: HTML5 • CSS3 • RESPONSIVE • SASS • UI DESIGN • BROWSER COMPATIBILITY

WORKING KNOWLEDGE: JAVASCRIPT . WCAG . PHP . ASP.NET MVC4 . GIT . CMS



WORK EXPERIENCE

CLIXAGEN, LONDON, ON

FRONTEND DEVELOPER & UI DESIGNER

DECEMBER 2014 - PRESENT

DUTIES: Building corporate websites and applications. Design clean user interfaces for multiple web applications system backends. Also take designs into html5 / css3 frameworks and produce final code in VIsual studio MVC4 web applications.

4 COLOUR DESIGNS, WOODSTOCK, ON

NOVEMBER 2012 - DECEMBER 2014

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

DUTIES: Coverted designed templates in Photo and coverted into Zurb foundation framework, Used tools such as HTML5/ CSS3 / SASS/ YOEMAN/ GRUNT to increase production time on the very tight deadlines to be met. Also managed web hosting servers and offered tech support to any issues that araised.

CRPU, TILLSONBURG, ON

SEPTEMBER 2010 - OCTOBER 2012

MULTIMEDIA COORDINATOR

DUTIES: Built and managed online store for all members across Canada, design and printed yearly stats book for all race results with members stats. Worked directly with Ricoh printing to decrease print cost on final production. Provided and trained office staff with online store support and techinal issues.



EDUCATION

WESTERVELT COLLEGE, LONDON ON

WEB DESIGN PROFESSIONAL GRADUATE, PRESIDENTAL HONOURS

COURSE OUTLINE: Provided me with the skills I needed to build interactive websites and the motivation to learn outside the class and take on freelancing projects to help increase my skills in coding and design concepts

TEAMTREEHOUSE

JAVASCRIPT FULL STACK

CURRENTLY LEARNING

ZEND PHP

FOUNDATIONS & HIGHER STRUCTURES

JULY 2013

UWO ONLINE

INTRO INTO PHP & MYSQL

APRIL 2012



SOFTWARE & TOOLS

ABOBE SUITE CC • MAC OSX • WINDOWS • UBUNTU LINUX • VM CLOUD HOSTING

SUBLIME TEXT MATE • YOEMAN • GRUNT/GULP • COMMAND LINE • EMAIL SERVICES

MICROSOFT VISUAL STUDIO • GOOGLE DRIVE/DROPBOX SERVICES • BOOTSTRAP/ZURB FRAMEWORK

IMAGE OPTIM • FIREFOX/CHROME DEVELOPER TOOLS • YAHOO YSLOW • MS OFFICE 365